(melancholy piano music)
♪ I will not make the same
mistakes that you did ♪
♪ I will not let myself 'cause
my heart so much misery ♪
♪ I will not break the way you did ♪
♪ You fell so hard ♪
♪ I've learned the hard way
to never let it get that far ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I never stray too
far from the sidewalk ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I learned to play on the
safe side so I don't get hurt ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I find it hard to trust not only me ♪
♪ But everyone around me ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I am afraid ♪
♪ I lose my way ♪
♪ And it's not too long
before you point it out ♪
♪ I cannot cry ♪
♪ Because I know that's
weakness in your eyes ♪
♪ I'm forced to fake a smile, a laugh ♪
♪ Every day of my life ♪
♪ My heart can't possibly break ♪
♪ When it wasn't even
whole to start with ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I never stray too
far from the sidewalk ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I learned to play on the
safe side so I don't get hurt ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I find it hard to trust not only me ♪
♪ But everyone around me ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I am afraid ♪
♪ I watched you die ♪
♪ I heard you cry ♪
♪ Every night in your sleep ♪
♪ I was so young ♪
♪ You should have known
better than to lean on me ♪
♪ You never thought of anyone else ♪
♪ You just saw your pain ♪
♪ And now I cry in the
middle of the night ♪
♪ For the same damn thing ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I never stray too
far from the sidewalk ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I learned to play on the
safe side so I don't get hurt ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I try my hardest just
to forget everything ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
♪ I don't know how to let anyone else in ♪
♪ Because of you I'm ashamed
of my life because it's empty ♪
♪ Because of you I am afraid ♪
♪ Because of you ♪
(melancholy piano music)